bag tag th
th MAG fifth
but as an hour thing and very
iffy how about her
missing the boat the toy home
dual I shave my head the
or do I just let the growth that
happened
the while
so
if the fed
light of god as bright and so
she is talking about Amanda and
on
let's let's not dig jump into it
hit here we go
OK at a wide
copyrighted music enhancer
basket passable and that
the head in
front of
on
cited, I don't know where the
footage is a staff
OK we play that video the other
day
write what is this here
this is her and Jamaal Bryant
the city
of
you know what on the stars date
rape wants right
daybreak sounds like it if it
sounds right
I allow the person who
gave me a different
the reasons excuses of to get an
opportunity
to have me partially on clove
and here we have this out that
and on
day and dangerous as an advice
and I can only hold
that you are able to get therapy
for yours
I am telling you
right
a he's
where now under in a vast tell
of which NSA is the
jazz into it just dawned on
doing don't do it
the time is a know what this
means
and that playing
while
the bid
and hang
the hang
yes
the shame
the new
right
of way she estimates that she
has been
operating she's been practicing
the without a license
here
thus cause this
cause this and get the volume of
the Ken
right
when I was at this as this
hypnotherapy school right
they taught me about how old in
the
that the head of therapists
years before I had this training
O
she was Ivan
but I have not had my
hypnotherapy
right
pretending to two B
while
but this doesn't
the tunnel and that means
of
I just wanna do this row quit
because
the ear many long ago to install
Graham
Amanda here it is a man does
Seles
the news follow
thank you on follow to help with
that
to hell with that
the Commish is well either
old
to
the bank
the lead gracious,
the new
year
the loan
the name come full
fall migrations
missed a step forward
yet as problematic
the all while
all my
in
that she not
a while
a well
the hang
the law
a while
the hang
rest of us go
what is she talking about
and yes it open this was what
was you call it
nothing better
news from the get this down on
the screen
and an honest
nine top yard dogleg
atoll citizens a clip in here
less
ideal and play that the two
ranchland
many fast forward
the new
act of
the O
the actor Bryant was that
calls data Bryant
the ANC and problematic
the Mias perspective
the Ivester questioned
rights
a disrespect
i.e.
for having me go in a different
direction
their bus for the grace of god
go I
then unhappy that it is not to
and let me go let me see if I
still have on
is at a 24 of
OK added 2412 but no is 247 OK
OK OK OK OK
OK so hour show you all a video
this one right here erasmo boy I
forget his name from
their
car
patio if I've never seen ended
in a black woman
right
to
party ever seen him today one of
those
because
the six winning and can take
this off-
money puts money put the son
back up one year because
the
O mike they hold on
I don't know
of
this and
a top
of
the
yacht Nissen
the Abu
yup
I writes a
needed July
then
when I saw him one on saw this
is not
then when I saw him
an hole he was showing himself
to be
I may sell LAN special as
was of a musician we played
all while
bag sixth to eighth of a youth
th cell death and
they only know
if the magazine bag,
zest of graduates
so that's me if
while
the somebody doesn't have sounds
either we have the movement
breaks
and I'm OK with that if
I'm all right if all caring
widower play the video clip
on
wouldn't play from Jesse Desi
wills on video
because she plays the whole
clear and
II think the clip that
demonstrates
a locked
it demonstrates a lot
the OK
the Cahill ago
its friendly responsible
for their children's
the old Ronald on
while this woman she's just so
ignorant
the data out there is clear that
data is clear that
the
of why she's talking everybody
felt is quiet
the same
she starts saying on attacking
to the people who think that she
was right
so she is provoking
each and
and for verbally abusive
relationships I can see it
I can see it
the end and the producers
sciences
of
dental parenting is absolutely
boundaries driven
the hang
so real is saying and I know
the well how much do you all
stayed there trying to
listen
to me just continue one forward
the synapses you mean like the
brain synapse
the we talking about Synopsys
I know who you're talking about
no
of
on
I'm just gonna say this please
as a trained a person
as a person with credentials
if there's anybody here that
Irish audio clip of Cheyenne
and in desk lead
she is revealing somebody who
she claims
of all its not playing
and then start again
here
to
jump and Joe brown was in my DM
asking for help
have you ever heard me say that
everything that we say here is
between you and I
why
all
this is a video that at
everything set off Jan
the ball
and
a fifth 5th
six
the of the San
missing
to Canada said it
then killed
2000 W
I am telling you that
it is inappropriate
I'm asking you whether or not is
if she said
if she said Kimberly Jones from
Oklahoma
or from Salt Lake City you talk
and all I can say to you one
that is
and alerts you to 01
I'm not coming in their lives
in some very tender
rights and their own emotional
regulation
to hold me when I cannot hold
myself
to beat them levelheaded person
when I am
dismayed elated
she stays starting
and the moments that ally become
and able to trust her because
she stays consistent
to pay of tension
my therapist said network won
this right here
to something a little more
healthy
you have to argue have to
are ideas get back to the video
sold
and
arrived
the the sound went back out
two on up
here let's go all the way back
the fifth 5th
six to
Pacific
the center this
on
the
tip
of my goodness
for
you can't blame him
fifth
so
O I'm gonna get
I'm gonna get blasted an
embarrassed O
behaving this way
the top
which is untrue
that
body shows the DMS hammock show
you
so these other DMS that he had
blanked out her phone number
before posting the DM
to shave on the other hand out
that this man's name
own owls
are right now there we have it
Amanda Seles has
lost the plot entirely
she's completely lost the plot
the ear
the fifth
the
she has no qualifications
brilliantly harder she was
talking about
and yes
the we all know that
you have it it it it it it it
the hang
the walls while he went off
of mind that if
on
Jan things are looking nice to
me behind the scenes
a glove I started I started
packing up my staff
fifth day of the NE
,
fifth is crazy so
missy what we're going to listen
to hear
we came in listening to some
reggae
AA of death
of th E,
you have an
S.F.
,
SSA AG six, and
fifth
and sixth U.S. FMLA,
half, sixth, if not unduly of
magma
th if the FAA guidelines and
ready for some reason
magazine this is
an
acted as if mold
all right but the
bald
all right here for me show you
all this
the right if
film
the teaching self worth
the mind Edmonds
thank you on
,
home
a right
self and it did affect fact that
A,
I'm getting needs some on
NASDAQ in two out what you call
it
let us get into the staff of
lessons
,
Coleman
Bonneville salt until barley now
, my goodness
the any help you right here
then go
Nadia Connors will be shown on
my screen
OK a messy lessee on
call move
, with low water
here it is
pulled a ride a city staff of
lessons Jan
up a
room
in lizabeth
either any given a warning
and as you come in his coming
after my warning
the 15
absolutely
the OK
cocaine
three myself of lessons
OK
one myself a blessing type SL L
and let me know
myself a blessing is in all of
this Israel a about
having the
unkind
Oken
awry so
and I am going to
th bang sixth
th
of
fifth